Guide to the Rand School of Social Science Records TAM.007
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Administrative Records, 1901-1956
  The American Socialist Society files also include extensive minutes (XIII:A:16) and papers relating to annual meetings (XIII:A:17). The minutes file contains valuable information about policies and events affecting the operations of the Rand School. It is recommended that these minutes as well as the American Socialist Society reports (XIII:A:15) be used in conjunction withthe Rand School Board of Directors' minutes. The annual meetings file contains correspondence and related papers of relatively minor importance. It should be pointed out that the papers pertaining to the annual meetings alsoinclude a frame number designation for each year in the file. For example, the papers relating to the 1950 annual meeting will have the frame number, XIII:A:17:1950.
  - Subseries IA: Rand School Boards/Minutes, 1907-1956
    - Rand School Society Minutes, May 6, 1907-Sep 13, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      General note
      Film R-7124, Reel 29: Frame XIII:A:1
    - Educational Council Minutes and Reports, Nov 7, 1919-1921 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 29: Frame XIII:A:2
    - Finance Committee Minutes, Feb 6, 1926-Feb 14, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 29: Frame XIII:A:3
    - Rand Educational Institute: Minutes, Certificate of Incorporation, and By-Laws, Mar 11, 1939-1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Film R-7124, Reel 29: Frame XIII:A:4
    - Rand School Board of Directors Correspondence, 1917-1944 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 29: Frame XIII:A:5
    - Rand School Board of Directors Correspondence, 1945-Jan 1956, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Rand School Board of Directors: Reports and Memoranda to the Board, 1916-1925 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Film R-7124, Reel 29: Frame XIII:A:6
    - Rand School Board of Directors: Reports and Memoranda to the Board, 1926-1930 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Rand School Board of Directors: Reports and Memoranda to the Board, 1931-1935 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Rand School Board of Directors: Reports and Memoranda to the Board, 1936-Oct 28, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Rand School Board of Directors: Reports and Memoranda of the Board, Oct 1926-Feb 17, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 29: Frame XIII:A:7
    - Rand School Board of Directors: Minutes and Resolutions (incomplete), Mar 25, 1906-Feb 23, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 29: Frame XIII:A:8
    - Rand School Board of Directors: Minutes and Resolutions, Jun 14, 1926-Dec 16, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Rand School Board of Directors: Minutes and Resolutions, Jan 21, 1936-Aug 14, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Rand School Board of Directors: Minutes and Resolutions, Jan 6, 1941-Dec 7, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Rand School Board of Directors: Minutes and Resolutions (incomplete), Nov 15, 1949-Sep 29, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Rand School Board of Directors: Minutes of a Joint Meeting with the Finance Committee of the American Socialist Society (A.S.S.), Jan 4, 1928, Jan 9, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 29: Frame XIII:A:9
  - Subseries IB: American Socialist Society, 1901-1956
    - American Socialist Society: General and Background Papers, Oct 1, 1901-1953 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 29: Frame XIII:A:10
    - Lusk Committee Investigation of the A.S.S.: Sworn Deposition by Isaac M. Sackin re the History & Function of the A.S.S., Oct 1918 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Film R-7124, Reel 29: Frame XIII:A:11a
    - Lusk Committee Investigation of the A.S.S.: Resolution Authorizing the Lusk Investigation, Mar 20, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Lusk Committee Investigation of the A.S.S.: Miscellaneous Affadavits, Exhibits, etc. re the Court Cases and Committee Investigation, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Lusk Committee Investigation of the A.S.S.: "Statement of Facts" by the A.S.S., 1919 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Lusk Committee Investigation of the A.S.S.: "Answers to Charges" Made by the Committee, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Lusk Committee Investigation of the A.S.S.: Legal Documents re the Issuance of a Search Warrant, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Lusk Committee Investigation of the A.S.S.: List of Documents Produced before the Committee, Jun 27, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Lusk Committee Investigation of the A.S.S.: N.Y. County Supreme Court "The People of the State of N.Y. vs American Socialist Society", Jul 8, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Lusk Committee Investigation of the A.S.S.: Inventory of Items Seized at the Rand School, Jul 8, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Lusk Committee Investigation of the A.S.S.: Subpoena Ordering Bertha Mailly to Appear before the Committee, Jul 8, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Lusk Committee Investigation of the A.S.S.: Copy of Letter from Samuel Untermeyer (Counsel for the A.S.S.) to Senator Luck, Jul 9, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Lusk Committee Investigation of the A.S.S.: Legal Papers. Attempt of the A.S.S. to Prohibit Circulation of the Confiscated Documents, Jul 14, 1919, Jul 15, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Lusk Committee Investigation of the A.S.S.: Letters Written to the A.S.S. by Interested Third Parties, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Lusk Committee Investigation of the A.S.S.: Broadside - "The Case of the Rand School", 1919 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Lusk Committee Investigation of the A.S.S.: Press Releases by the Rand School, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Lusk Committee Investigation of the A.S.S.: Untitled Incomplete Manuscript re the Case (by the A.S.S.), 1919 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Lusk Committee: Newspaper Clippings, miscellaneous, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      NOT FILMED
    - United States of America vs. American Socialist Society and Scott Nearing, United States District Court, Mar 18, 1919-Feb 19, 1920 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      Film R-7124, Reel 29: Frame XIII:A:11b
    - The People of the State of New York against American Socialist Society, Court of Appeals of the State of New York, Feb 26, 1922, May 1, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      Film R-7124, Reel 29: Frame XIII:A:11c
    - A.S.S.: Correspondence, Nov 19, 1909-Dec 30, 1955, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
      Film R-7124, Reel 29: Frame XIII:A:12
    - A.S.S.: Correspondence relating to its tax exempt status, Jan 13, 1939-Oct 13, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      Film R-7124, Reel 29: Frame XIII:A:13
    - A.S.S.: Mimeographed correspondence to members, Dec 13, 1926-Jul 23, 1946, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:14
    - A.S.S.: Reports to Board and Members, 1911, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:15
    - A.S.S.: Reports to Board and Members, 1930-1934 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - A.S.S.: Reports to Board and Members, 1935-1939 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - A.S.S.: Reports to Board and Members, 1940-1943 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - A.S.S.: Reports to Board and Members, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - A.S.S.: Reports to Board, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - A.S.S. Minutes: Board & General Meetings, Nov 25, 1905-Dec 6, 1907 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:16
    - A.S.S. Minutes: Board & General Meetings, Sep 11, 1908-Dec 3, 1909 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - A.S.S. Minutes: Board & General Meetings, Feb 7, 1910-Sep 30, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - A.S.S. Minutes: Board & General Meetings, Jan 25, 1913-Apr 30, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - A.S.S. Minutes: Board & General Meetings, May 17, 1918-Nov 13, 1922 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - A.S.S. Minutes: Board & General Meetings, Jan 8, 1923-Dec 17, 1923 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - A.S.S. Minutes: Board & General Meetings, Jan 7, 1924-Dec 15, 1924 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - A.S.S. Minutes: Board & General Meetings, Jan 4, 1925-Mar 30, 1925 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - A.S.S. Minutes: Board & General Meetings, Jan 1, 1926-Nov 22, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - A.S.S. Minutes: Board & General Meetings (incomplete), Mar 11, 1927-Apr 14, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - A.S.S. Minutes: Board & General Meetings, Feb 10, 1931-Dec 11, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - A.S.S. Minutes: Board & General Meetings, Jan 12, 1932-Dec 11, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - A.S.S. Minutes: Board & General Meetings, Jan 16, 1933-Dec 11, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - A.S.S. Minutes: Board & General Meetings, Jan 15, 1934-Nov 23, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - A.S.S. Minutes: Board & General Meetings, Feb 15, 1935-Dec 22, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - A.S.S. Minutes: Board & General Meetings, Jan 13, 1936-Dec 5, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - A.S.S. Minutes: Board & General Meetings, Jan 21, 1937-Dec 5, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - A.S.S. Minutes: Board & General Meetings, Jan 3, 1940-Dec 13, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - A.S.S. Minutes: Board & General Meetings (incomplete), Apr 23, 1941-Mar 26, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - A.S.S. Annual Meeting, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1924
    - A.S.S. Annual Meeting, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1932
    - A.S.S. Annual Meeting, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1934
    - A.S.S. Annual Meeting, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1935
    - A.S.S. Annual Meetings (held Feb 28th, Dec 5th), 1941 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1941
    - A.S.S. Annual Meeting (held Jul 23rd), 1942 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1942
    - A.S.S. Annual Meeting (held Mar 26th), 1943 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1943
    - A.S.S. Annual Meetings (held Mar 31st, Nov 24th), 1944 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1944
    - A.S.S. Annual Meeting (held Mar 9th), 1945 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1945
    - A.S.S. Annual Meeting (held Apr 19th), 1946 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1946
    - A.S.S. Annual Meeting (held Mar 21st), 1947 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1947
    - A.S.S. Annual Meeting (held Mar 5th), 1948 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1948
    - A.S.S. Annual Meeting (held Apr 29th), 1949 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1949
    - A.S.S. Annual Meeting (held Mar 31st), 1950 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1950
    - A.S.S. Annual Meeting (held May 4th), 1951 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1951
    - A.S.S. Annual Meeting (held May 16th), 1952 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1952
    - A.S.S. Annual Meeting (held Apr 3rd), 1953 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1953
    - A.S.S. Annual Meeting (held Apr 2nd), 1954 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1954
    - A.S.S. Annual Meeting (held May 20th), 1955 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1955
    - A.S.S. Annual Meeting (held Jun 20th), 1956 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:1956
    - A.S.S. Annual Meeting, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:17:nd
    - A.S.S. Membership Lists, 1920, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:18
    - A.S.S. Membership Lists, Feb 18, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - A.S.S. Membership Lists, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - A.S.S. Membership Lists, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - A.S.S. Dues Records: Ledger, 1925-1933 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:19a
    - A.S.S. Dues Records: List, "Payment A.S.S. Dues", Feb 17, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:19b
    - A.S.S. Dues Records: Ledger of Members (including dues payments), 1940-1955 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:19c
    - A.S.S. Dues Records: List of Members in Arrears, Feb 1, 1942, Jun 15, 1942, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:19d
    - A.S.S. Dues Records: Correspondence, Feb 12, 1935-May 6, 1905 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:19e
    - A.S.S.: Transfer of title of the Rand School to the People's Educational Camp Society, Jan 5, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:A:20
- Series II: General Correspondence, 1913-1957
  The general correspondence constitutes the largest quantity of records in the Rand School collection. Most of the items in this series pertain to the period, 1930-1949, although there is correspondence covering the entire history of the Rand School. The correspondence is arranged in chronological order, with undated items located at the end of the series. Much of the correspondence reflects such routine matters as handling inquiries about course offerings or teaching positions, mailing invitations to guest speakers, making arrangements for courses and lectures, and sponsoring fund raising events. Besides these items, there are several letters which discuss the Lusk Committee's investigation of the Rand School, unemployment during the Depression, the Socialist Party split in the mid 1930s, and the affairs of the New Leader.Most of the correspondence is from the executive offices of the Rand School, particularly from Algernon Lee, Bertha H. Mailly, William E. Bohn, John L. Afros, and Theodore Schapiro. Other correspondents with letters of more than routine interest are Norman Thomas, Upton Sinclair, Charles Edward Russell, John M. Work, J. Mahlon Barnes, Clarence Senior, Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, and William C. Duffy.
  - General Correspondence, 1913-1920 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Film R-7124, Reel 30: Frame XIII:B
  - General Correspondence, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, 1921-1923 (Box 5, Folder 8, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, 1924-1925 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1926 - Apr 1926 (Box 5, Folder 11, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, May 1926 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1926-Dec 1926 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 14, Folder 10)
    Film R-7124, Reel 31: Frame XIII:B
  - General Correspondence, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1929-Feb 1929 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1929-Apr 1929 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, May 1929-Jun 1929 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1929-Aug 1929 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1929-Oct 1929 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1929-Dec 1929 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1930 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1930 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1930 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1930 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, May 1930 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1930 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1930 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1930 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1930 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1930 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1930 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1930 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence, 1930 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1931 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1931 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1931 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1931 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, May 1931 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1931 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1931 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1931 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1931 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1931 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1931 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1931 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1932 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1932 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1932 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence, May 1932 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1932 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1932 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1932 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1932 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1932 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1932 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1932 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1932 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - General Correspondence, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1, 1933-Jan 17, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 18, 1933-Jan 31, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1933 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Film R-7124, Reel 32: Frame XIII:B
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1, 1933-Mar 17, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 18, 1933-Mar 30, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1933 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, May 1, 1933-May 17, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, May 18, 1933-May 30, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1933 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1933 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1933 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1933 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1933 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1933 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1933 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1934 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1934 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1934 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1934 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, May 1934 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1934 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1934 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1934 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1934 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1934 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1934 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Film R-7124, Reel 33: Frame XIII:B
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1934 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1935 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1935 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1935 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1935 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, May 1935 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1935 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1935 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1935 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1935 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1935 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1935 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1935 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, 1935 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1936 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1936 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1, 1936- Mar 11, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 12, 1936-Mar 31, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1936 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, May 1936 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Film R-7124, Reel 34: Frame XIII:B
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1936 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1936 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1936 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1936 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1936 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1936 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1936 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1937 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1937 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1937 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1937 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, May 1937 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1937 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1937 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1937 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1937 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1937 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1937 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1937 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1938 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1938 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1938 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1938 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, May 1938 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1938 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1938 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1938 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1938 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1938 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1938 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1938 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1939 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1, 1939-Feb 12, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 13, 1939-Feb 25, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1, 1939-Mar 19, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 20, 1939-Mar 31, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1, 1939-Apr 10, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 11, 1939-Apr 30, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, May 1, 1939-May 9, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, May 10, 1939-May 31, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1939 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Film R-7124, Reel 35: Frame XIII:B
  - General Correspondence, Jun 15, 1939-Jun 30, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1939 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1939 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1939 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1939 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1939 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1939 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1940 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1940 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1940 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1940 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, May 1940 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1940 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, Jul 1940 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, Aug 1940 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, Sep 1940 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, Oct 1940 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, Nov 1940 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, Dec 1940 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, Jan 1941 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, Feb 1941 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, Mar 1941 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, Apr 1941 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence, May 1941 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence, Jun 1941 (Box 15, Folder 19)